<resources>
    <string name="appName">School Subjects</string>

    <string name="englishTxt">English and language arts are two of the most basic and widely taught subjects in
        United States schools. The American National Council of Teachers of English separates English and language
        arts into five basic categories: reading, writing, speaking, listening and viewing.</string>

    <string name="mathsTxt">Mathematics is a fundamental part of human thought and logic, and integral to attempts at
        understanding the world and ourselves. Mathematics provides an effective way of building mental discipline and
        encourages logical reasoning and mental rigor. In addition, mathematical knowledge plays a crucial role in
        understanding the contents of other school subjects such as science, social studies, and even music and art.</string>

    <string name="chemistryTxt">Chemistry, the science that deals with the properties, composition, and structure of substances
        (defined as elements and compounds), the transformations they undergo, and the energy that is released or absorbed
        during these processes.</string>

    <string name="biologyTxt">Biology is the study of life and living organisms. General biology courses encompass many
        aspects of the science, such as ecology, genetics, paleontology, physiology and zoology. ... Topics include cell
        biology, human disease and genetics.</string>

    <string name="physicsTxt">Physics is the study of the properties of matter and their relationship with energy and forces.
        The study of physics can be divided into classical physics, relativity, and quantum mechanics. ... Classical physics
        concerns everyday sizes and velocities.</string>

    <string name="historyTxt">The Past Teaches Us About the Present
        Because history gives us the tools to analyze and explain problems in the past, it positions us to see patterns that
        might otherwise be invisible in the present – thus providing a crucial perspective for understanding (and solving!)
        current and future problems.</string>

    <string name="sociologyTxt">Sociology is a social science concerned with the study of society and human behaviour and
        relationships. ... The subject matter is diverse and can cover anything from race, social class, crime and law, poverty,
        education and more theoretical wider issues such as the impact of radical change to whole societies.</string>

    <string name="scienceTxt">Science is a universal subject that spans the branch of knowledge that examines the structure
        and behavior of the physical and natural world through observation and experiment. Science education is most commonly
        broken down into the following three fields: Biology, Chemistry, and Physics.</string>

    <string name="sportTxt">Playing sports teaches lessons of life, such as teamwork, accountability, self-confidence,
        responsibility, and self-discipline. Sports in school help prepare students to face the challenges of life. They
        enhance physical and mental abilities of students and help them achieve the goals of their life.</string>

</resources>
